Hi, in this lesson, you will get a quick hands-on in production to Google Guardian.
We will create a simple project and try out the main features so we can see how everything
works together.
And then in the next lesson, we will dive deeper and deeper and you will learn how to
use all these features with more details.
Okay, let me start my introduction with a detail in general.
So on the left side, so if you're not never used this detail or similar, like it will
be useful for you.
I will try to do it really short.
On the left side, you have the menu.
And navigation, you can use the exposure to see all your files in your project.
You can see the storage to sort of some words through your projects.
You can use the extensions to install some extensions, for example, the DM, some helpers
for your calls, some helpers for your quality detail.
So in the main windows, you don't see all the files you open, its content, what is inside.
And on the right side, you see the sidebar panel for the agent, agent is AI assistant.
You can chat here with AI to get help, to ask some questions, so I will click this miss.
And you can choose different modes, the different models, etc.
We'll dive into it in two later, all lessons.
Also, what is useful for you, you see this icon, so you can easily toggle agent, and you
can easily toggle the sidebar.
And you can also open the terminal, it's the place where you can write some commands.
Yeah?
So just remember this icon.
And if you'd like to go to settings, you can click on integrity, settings, and use the
integrity settings.
And this settings is especially for integrity, you can find here are some useful options
for your most AI usage.
Yeah.
And if you'd like to see the editor settings, you can click just editor settings.
And you can adjust here some forms, some sizes, some commands, etc.
OK, all let's open some project.
I will open, I think, right here, project, it's empty, I've just created it for this
use case.
Oh, but you see this message, just click, yes, I trust the authors.
It's kind of check if project you open, you really trust it, and the file is safe to
use.
Yeah.
OK.
So, we have our Antigravity Calendar project, I will create a file, I will create a file
right here, click new file, and make it calendar.js.
OK, the first feature I'd like to show you is stop completion.
It's when you start typing something, the Antigravity can understand and help you.
Like if I will start type plus, it already suggests me to create a calendar which extends
React component, I don't know why I'm component, but I just need the calendar class.
So I can continue typing and then it will suggest me so you see when I click up, suggest
me the new methods, I can click jump, so you see it help me to create something.
OK, this is a type completion in the next class, since you'll dive into it in more details,
you'll see the real use case because it's the simple one, it's not useful, plus, yes, but
you'll create something better.
I just want to show you the possibilities of PI with this code editor.
You can also use another option here, for example, when you select some part of code, you
can click chat, and it will send a part of code into your chat, and you can ask something.
For example, what does this line of code does, and you start it in conversation with
the ISO, it's syncing, it's analyze the code, and it will generate for you response.
So, and you see those based on the snippet you select, this is the JSX code, it creates
a generic container, and just inside random text calendar, so this is a two normal ways
how to work with anti-gravity detail. I'll show you more hacks in the next lessons, but
what is also important, and I'd like to explain it to you, please don't ask anti-gravity
to build an entire application from scratch. In one prompt, like build for me, I don't
know, those board application with users, payments, etc. It works best when you break
task into smaller, focused request, like work in step-by-step. I'll later in this course
you will see the prompt section where we will explain you the best techniques and patterns
how to write prompts. Hope this also works out. Please remember that you are responsible
for the code that anti-gravity generates, and you always need to verify it, review suggestions
before accepting them, and test the code to make sure it works as expected. Because AI
and not so smart, as we might say, it's kind of a junior developer, but home you need to
give a really detailed and clear instructions and always review the work. So, okay, you
can start with some simple prompts and add more details, you need it. So, and this remembers
the more details you give to your AI, and it's the better answer you get. So, this
is a was quick overview of anti-gravity, got the details short of AI possibilities. See in
the next lesson where I will dive into each feature in more details.